Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 43 Records, 1889-1968, I.; 49 bound volumes, 23 boxes, 1 official stamp
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1889-1968, I.A; 9 bound volumes, 20 boxes
    - Special General Meeting, August 5, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 278)
    - Board Meeting, August 8, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 279)
    - Board Meeting, August 10, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 280)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 281)
    - Special General Meeting, August 23, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 282)
    - Board Meeting, August 26, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 283)
    - Special General Meeting, August 31, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 284)
    - Board Meeting, September 7, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 285)
    - General Meeting, September 13, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 286)
    - Board Meeting, September 20, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 287)
    - Board Meeting, September 26 ,1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 288)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 289)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 290)
    - Board Meeting, October 6, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 291)
    - General Meeting, October 11, 1933, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 292)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 293)
    - Board Meeting, November 11, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 294)
    - General Meeting, November 8, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 295)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 296)
    - Board Meeting, November 28, 1933, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 297)
    - Board Meeting, December 8, 1933, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 298)
    - General Meeting, December 13, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 299)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 300)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 301)
    - General Meeting, January 19, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 302)
    - Board Meeting, January 16, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 303)
    - Board Meeting, January 24, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 304)
    - Board Meeting, January 27, 1934, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 305)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1934, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 306)
    - General Meeting, February 14, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 307)
    - Board Meeting, February 17, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 308)
    - Board Meeting, February 19, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 309)
    - Board Meeting, February 20, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 310)
    - Board Meeting, March 7, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 311)
    - General Meeting, March 14, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 312)
    - Board Meeting, March 27, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 313)
    - Board Meeting, April 3, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 314)
    - Board Meeting, April 7, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 315)
    - General Meeting, April 11, 1934, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 316)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 317)
    - Special General Meeting, April 25, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 318)
    - Board Meeting, May 1, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 319)
    - General Meeting, May 9, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 320)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1934, 3 leaves (Box 3, Item 321)
    - Board Meeting, May 18, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 322)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 323)
    - Board Meeting, June 27, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 324)
    - Board Meeting, July 10, 1934, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 325)
    - Board Meeting, July 17, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 326)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 327)
    - Board Meeting, July 21, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 328)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 329)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 330)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 331)
    - Special General Meeting, August 8, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 332)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 333)
    - Special General Meeting, August 22, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 334)
    - Board Meeting, August 27, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 335)
    - Board Meeting, September 1, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 336)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 337)
    - Board Meeting, September 20, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 338)
    - Board Meeting, October 3, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 339)
    - General Meeting, October 10, 1934, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 340)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 341)
    - Special General Meeting, October 17, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 342)
    - Board Meeting, October 23, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 343)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 344)
    - General Meeting, November 14, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 345)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 346)
    - Board Meeting, December 4, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 347)
    - General Meeting, December 12, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 348)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 349)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 350)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 351)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 352)
    - General Meeting, January 9, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 353)
    - Board Meeting, January 15, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 354)
    - Board Meeting, January 22, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 355)
    - Board Meeting, January 30, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 356)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 357)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1935, 4 leaves (Box 3, Item 358)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 359)
    - General Meeting, February 13, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 360)
    - Board Meeting, February 21, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 361)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 362)
    - Board Meeting, March 4, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 363)
    - General Meeting, March 13, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 364)
    - Board Meeting, March 14, 1935, 9 leaves (Box 3, Item 365)
    - Board Meeting, March 16, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 366)
    - Board Meeting, March 25, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 367)
    - Board Meeting, April 4, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 368)
    - General Meeting, April 10, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 369)
    - Board Meeting, April 11, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 370)
    - Board Meeting, April 25, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 371)
    - Board Meeting, May 7, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 372)
    - General Meeting, May 8, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 373)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 374)
    - Board Meeting, May 22, 1935, 3 leaves (Box 3, Item 375)
    - Board Meeting, May 23, 1935, 4 leaves (Box 3, Item 376)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 377)
    - Board Meeting, June 6, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 378)
    - Special Board Meeting, June 17, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 379)
    - Board Meeting, June 20, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 380)
    - Board Meeting, June 27, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 381)
    - Board Meeting, July 6, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 382)
    - Board Meeting, July 11, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 383)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 384)
    - Board Meeting, July 18, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 385)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 386)
    - Board Meeting, July 23, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 387)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 388)
    - Board Meeting, July 30, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 389)
    - Board Meeting, August 8, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 390)
    - Special General Meeting, August 15, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 391)
    - Board Meeting, August 20, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 392)
    - Board Meeting, August 24, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 393)
    - Board Meeting, August 29, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 394)
    - General Meeting, September 11, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 395)
    - Board Meeting, September 18, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 396)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 397)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 398)
    - Board Meeting, October 2, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 399)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 400)
    - General Meeting, October 9, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 3, Item 401)
    - Board Meeting, October 15, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 402)
    - Board Meeting, October 17, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 403)
    - Board Meeting, October 31, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 404)
    - Board Meeting, November 7, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 3, Item 405)
    - General Meeting, November 13, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 406)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 407)
    - Board Meeting, November 21, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 408)
    - Board Meeting, November 23, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 409)
    - Board Meeting, November 26, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 410)
    - Board Meeting, December 5, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 411)
    - Board Meeting, December 12, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 412)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 16, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 413)
    - Board Meeting, December 19, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 414)
    - Board Meeting, December 26, 1935, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 415)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 416)
    - Board Meeting, January 9, 1936, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 417)
    - Board Meeting, January 16, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 418)
    - Board Meeting, January 18, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 419)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 420)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 421)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1935, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 422)
    - Board Meeting, February 22, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 423)
    - Board Meeting, February 29, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 424)
    - Board Meeting, March 3, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 425)
    - Board Meeting, March 7, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 426)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 10, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 427)
    - General Meeting, March 11, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 428)
    - Board Meeting, March 14, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 429)
    - Board Meeting, March 21, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 430)
    - Board Meeting, March 28, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 431)
    - Board Meeting, April 4, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 432)
    - General Meeting, April 8, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 433)
    - Board Meeting, April 11, 1936, 7 leaves (Box 4, Item 434)
    - Board Meeting, April 18, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 435)
    - Board Meeting, April 25, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 436)
    - Board Meeting, May 2, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 437)
    - Board Meeting, May 9, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 438)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 439)
    - Board Meeting, May 23, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 440)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 441)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1936, 3 leaves (Box 4, Item 442)
    - Board Meeting, June 18, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 443)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 444)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 445)
    - Board Meeting, July 11, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 446)
    - Board Meeting, July 18, 1936, 3 leaves (Box 4, Item 447)
    - Board Meeting, July 21, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 448)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 449)
    - Board Meeting, August 1, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 450)
    - Board Meeting, August 3, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 451)
    - Board Meeting, August 5, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 452)
    - Board Meeting, August 8, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 453)
    - General Meeting, August 12, 1936, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 454)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 455)
    - Board Meeting, August 15, 1936, 3 leaves (Box 4, Item 456)
    - Special General Meeting, August 19, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 457)
    - Board Meeting, August 22, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 458)
    - Board Meeting, August 29, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 459)
    - Board Meeting, September 5, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 460)
    - Board Meeting, September 12, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 461)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 462)
    - Board Meeting, September 19, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 463)
    - Board Meeting, September 26, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 464)
    - Board Meeting, September 29, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 465)
    - Board Meeting, October 3, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 466)
    - Board Meeting, October 10, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 467)
    - General Meeting, October 14, 1936, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 468)
    - Board Meeting, October 17, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 469)
    - Board Meeting, October 23, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 470)
    - Board Meeting, October 31, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 471)
    - Board Meeting, November 7, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 472)
    - General Meeting, November 11, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 473)
    - Board Meeting, November 14, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 474)
    - Board Meeting, November 21, 1936, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 475)
    - Board Meeting, November 28, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 476)
    - General Meeting, December 9, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 477)
    - Board Meeting, December 12, 1936, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 478)
    - Board Meeting, December 12, 1936 [i.e., December 19], 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 479)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1936, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 480)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 481)
    - Board Meeting, January 9, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 482)
    - General Meeting, January 13, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 483)
    - Board Meeting, January 16, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 484)
    - Board Meeting, January 23, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 485)
    - Board Meeting, January 20, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 486)
    - Board Meeting, February 6, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 487)
    - General Meeting, February 10, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 488)
    - Board Meeting, February 13, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 489)
    - Board Meeting, February 20, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 490)
    - Special General Meeting, February 22, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 491)
    - Board Meeting, February 27, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 492)
    - Special Board Meeting, Special Board Meeting, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 493)
    - Board Meeting, March 6, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 494)
    - General Meeting, March 10, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 495)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 496)
    - Board Meeting, March 20, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 497)
    - Special General Meeting, March 21, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 498)
    - Board Meeting, March 25, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 499)
    - Board Meeting, April 3, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 500)
    - Board Meeting, April 10, 1937, 8 leaves (Box 4, Item 501)
    - Board Meeting, April 12, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 502)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 503)
    - Board Meeting, April 24, 1937, 4 leaves (Box 4, Item 504)
    - Board Meeting, May 1, 1937, 3 leaves (Box 4, Item 505)
    - Board Meeting, May 8, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 506)
    - Board Meeting, May 14, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 507)
    - Board Meeting, May 22, 1937, 7 leaves (Box 4, Item 508)
    - Board Meeting, May 29, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 509)
    - Board Meeting, June 5, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 510)
    - Board Meeting, June 12, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 511)
    - Board Meeting, June 19, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 512)
    - Special Board Meeting, June 22, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 513)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 514)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 515)
    - Special General Meeting, July 7, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 516)
    - Board Meeting, July 10, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 517)
    - Board Meeting, July 17, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 518)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 519)
    - Board Meeting, July 24, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 520)
    - Board Meeting, July 31, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 521)
    - Special General Meeting, August 5, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 522)
    - Board Meeting, August 6, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 523)
    - Board Meeting, August 7, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 524)
    - Board Meeting, August 12, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 525)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 526)
    - Board Meeting, August 18, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 527)
    - Special General Meeting, August 19, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 528)
    - Board Meeting, August 21, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 529)
    - Special General Meeting, August 26, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 530)
    - Board Meeting, August 28, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 531)
    - Board Meeting, September 4, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 4, Item 532)
    - General Meeting, September 8, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 533)
    - Board Meeting, September 11, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 534)
    - Board Meeting, September 18, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 535)
    - Board Meeting, September 25, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 536)
    - Board Meeting, October 2, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 537)
    - Board Meeting, October 9, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 538)
    - General Meeting, October 13, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 539)
    - Board Meeting, October 16, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 4, Item 540)
    - Board Meeting, October 23, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 541)
    - Board Meeting, October 30, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 542)
    - Board Meeting, November 6, 1937, 3 leaves (Box 5, Item 543)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 6, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 544)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 8, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 545)
    - General Meeting, November 10, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 546)
    - Board Meeting, November 12, 1937, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 547)
    - Board Meeting, November 20, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 548)
    - Board Meeting, November 26, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 549)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 550)
    - Board Meeting, December 11, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 551)
    - Board Meeting, December 18, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 552)
    - Board Meeting, December 23, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 553)
    - Board Meeting, December 30, 1937, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 554)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 555)
    - Board Meeting, January 8, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 556)
    - General Meeting, January 12, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 557)
    - Board Meeting, January 12, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 558)
    - Board Meeting, January 15, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 559)
    - Board Meeting, January 22, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 560)
    - Special General Meeting, January 26, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 561)
    - Board Meeting, January 26, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 562)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 563)
    - Board Meeting, February 6, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 564)
    - General Meeting, February 9, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 565)
    - Board Meeting, February 12, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 566)
    - Board Meeting, February 19, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 567)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 568)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 569)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 570)
    - Board Meeting, March 5, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 571)
    - General Meeting, March 9, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 572)
    - Board Meeting, March 10, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 573)
    - Board Meeting, March 12, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 574)
    - Board Meeting, March 19, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 575)
    - Board Meeting, March 23, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 576)
    - Board Meeting, March 26, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 577)
    - Board Meeting, March 30, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 578)
    - Board Meeting, April 9, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 579)
    - General Meeting, April 13, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 580)
    - Board Meeting, April 16, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 581)
    - Board Meeting, April 23, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 582)
    - Board Meeting, April 28, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 583)
    - Board Meeting, April 29, 1938, 3 leaves (Box 5, Item 584)
    - Board Meeting, May 7, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 585)
    - General Meeting, May 11, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 586)
    - Board Meeting, May 14, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 587)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 588)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 589)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 590)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 591)
    - Board Meeting, June 11, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 592)
    - Board Meeting, June 18, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 593)
    - Board Meeting, June 23, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 594)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 595)
    - Board Meeting, June 29, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 596)
    - Board Meeting, July 2, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 597)
    - Board Meeting, July 9, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 598)
    - Board Meeting, July 14, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 599)
    - Board Meeting, July 16, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 600)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 601)
    - Board Meeting, July 23, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 602)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 603)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 604)
    - Board Meeting, July 30, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 605)
    - Board Meeting, August 1, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 606)
    - Board Meeting, August 6, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 607)
    - General Meeting, August 10, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 608)
    - Board Meeting, August 11, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 609)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 610)
    - Board Meeting, August 20, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 611)
    - Board Meeting, August 27, 1938, 3 leaves (Box 5, Item 612)
    - Board Meeting, September 3, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 613)
    - Board Meeting, September 8, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 614)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 615)
    - General Meeting, September 14, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 616)
    - Board Meeting, September 15, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 617)
    - Board Meeting, September 22, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 618)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 619)
    - Board Meeting, October 1, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 620)
    - Board Meeting, October 8, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 621)
    - Board Meeting, October 15, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 622)
    - Board Meeting, October 22, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 623)
    - Board Meeting, October 28, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 624)
    - Board Meeting, October 29, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 625)
    - Board Meeting, November 5, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 626)
    - General Meeting, November 9, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 627)
    - Board Meeting, November 11, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 628)
    - Board Meeting, November 19, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 629)
    - Board Meeting, November 26, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 630)
    - Board Meeting, December 10, 1938, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 631)
    - Board Meeting, December 17, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 632)
    - Board Meeting, December 24, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 633)
    - Board Meeting, December 31, 1938, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 634)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1939, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 635)
    - Board Meeting, January 7, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 636)
    - General Meeting, January 11, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 637)
    - Board Meeting, January 14, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 638)
    - Board Meeting, January 17, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 639)
    - Board Meeting, January 21, 1939, 3 leaves (Box 5, Item 640)
    - Board Meeting, January 28, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 641)
    - Board Meeting, February 3, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 642)
    - General Meeting, February 8, 1939, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 643)
    - Board Meeting, February 11, 1939, 2 leaves (Box 5, Item 644)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1939, 1 leaf (Box 5, Item 645)
    - Board Meeting, February 18, 1939, 4 leaves (Box 5, Item 646)